[Math

](https://www.mathcha.io/) About [Open Editor](https://www.mathcha.io/editor)

Math  

=======================================================

This is privacy policy for "Mathcha website and Mathcha Online", for "Mathcha Notebook" (Offline version or Desktop version), please refer to this page: [Privacy Policy](https://www.mathcha.io/notebook/privacy-policy)

Thank you for visiting our Mathcha website. Mathcha regards our clients' privacy as one of our most important values. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal or confidential information ("Information").

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. This privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. Mathcha may update this privacy policy from time to time. Any changes to this policy will be posted on the website. We encourage you to review the actual privacy policy whenever you visit Mathcha website.

**Changes**

We will notify our users by E-mail about any significant changes to this privacy policy.

**Collection and Use of Information from Us (Mathcha)**

We collect Information from you when you:

a) Register free Account - User's name and e-mail address

b) Payment for Mathcha Notebook (Offline or Desktop version) - Only e-mail address

Your Information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.

Your document data is stored in Heroku Server, and Images are stored in Amazon Cloud Storage.

You are able to delete your documents (in Document Views left sidebar), document data is removed from Heroku Server.

You are able to delete your images (in Image Manager dialog), Images are removed from Amazon Cloud Storage.

For your personal data (email, username,..), please request to team@mathcha.io if you want to delete from your account.

For whole account deletion (with all related information), request to email team@mathcha.io to initiate account deletion process.

We don't have any advertisment, so we don't use your information for any advertisment.

Reference:

Amazon Cloud Storage Privacy: [https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy-faq/](https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy-faq/)

Heroku Security: [https://devcenter.heroku.com/articles/security-privacy-compliance](https://devcenter.heroku.com/articles/security-privacy-compliance)

**Collection and Use of Information from Stripe service for Payment**

We are using third party [Stripe](https://stripe.com/) for processing payment (very well-known for payment gateway), we (Mathcha) **do not** store any below information (for PCI compliant). But Stripe service may need :

a) Your Name

b) Your Address

c) Your Card Information

Reference:

Stripe Security: [https://stripe.com/docs/security/stripe](https://stripe.com/docs/security/stripe)

PCI Compliance: [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Payment\_Card\_Industry\_Data\_Security\_Standard](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Payment_Card_Industry_Data_Security_Standard)

**Cookies**

We use cookies. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. Cookie typically contains the name of the website, the storage time, and a unique number that identifies your browser. Detailed information about the possibilities and ways of handling cookies are available in the settings of your web browser.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Final provisions**

In matters not covered by this Privacy policy, the [Terms of Service](https://www.mathcha.io/terms-of-service) are applicable.

2018-2023 Mathcha.io  
team@mathcha.io  

All rights reserved
